[{"answer": "I just don't think you're being fair", "docId": "Basquiat.txt", "asentId": 3, "question": "I need this", "qsentId": 2}, {"answer": "my friend, could you get me a Phillips screwdriver", "docId": "Basquiat.txt", "asentId": 5, "question": "A my friend head. From the toolbox", "qsentId": 4}, {"answer": "What're you doing? You're doing something", "docId": "Basquiat.txt", "asentId": 7, "question": "Don't give him anything, man. Your art's worth a lot. Trade. That's what real artists do with each other. Besides, he'll just use you. He's famous for that", "qsentId": 6}, {"answer": "You heard of my friend. I made    that niggah. I'm my friend. Didn't    you read", "docId": "Basquiat.txt", "asentId": 9, "question": "I can put you in the ring with him. Even book the dates.  But those big boys know how to fight. The", "qsentId": 8}, {"answer": "my friend lives in that place, that place", "docId": "Basquiat.txt", "asentId": 11, "question": "that place, that place", "qsentId": 10}, {"answer": "that place's in that place", "docId": "Basquiat.txt", "asentId": 13, "question": "It's in that place", "qsentId": 12}, {"answer": "that place, that place", "docId": "Basquiat.txt", "asentId": 15, "question": "that place", "qsentId": 14}, {"answer": "It's in that place", "docId": "Basquiat.txt", "asentId": 17, "question": "I think it's in that place", "qsentId": 16}, {"answer": "that place", "docId": "Basquiat.txt", "asentId": 19, "question": "It's in that place", "qsentId": 18}, {"answer": "They're just words", "docId": "Basquiat.txt", "asentId": 21, "question": "Where? Do you ask Miles where he got that note from? Where do you take your words from?  Everywhere", "qsentId": 20}, {"answer": "Oh, that's a", "docId": "Basquiat.txt", "asentId": 23, "question": "I use a lot of colors", "qsentId": 22}, {"answer": "I'm not black", "docId": "Basquiat.txt", "asentId": 25, "question": "Not what", "qsentId": 24}, {"answer": "OK. One last thing. Is there any anger in you? Any anger in your work", "docId": "Basquiat.txt", "asentId": 27, "question": "Tell me about it. What are you angry about", "qsentId": 26}]